ara-bux.com 2009-03-11

# ARA-Bux | .click .view .earn

Privacy Policy

**ARA-Bux.com is owned by ARA-UK.com Ltd..**  
This policy covers all sites produced by ARA-UK.com Ltd.. ARA-UK.com Ltd. is committed to protecting your privacy online. This privacy policy informs you what personal information ARA-UK.com Ltd. collects and the purposes for which it uses this information. This policy may change from time to time. 

**Disclosures** ARA-UK.com Ltd. may disclose your information, under strict terms of confidentiality and restriction of use, to partners of ARA-UK.com Ltd. who supply services on behalf of ARA-UK.com Ltd. and who require to process personal data in the provision of such services. When you use ARA-UK.com Ltd. you are consenting to the disclosure of your personal information to ARA-UK.com Ltd. partners, unless you have otherwise informed us that you do not wish us to disclose your personal information. However, under certain circumstances the force of law may require the provision of information to legal authorities. In order to safeguard the interests of its subscribers ARA-UK.com Ltd. will comply with any such legally binding request. 

**Information we collect**  
Identifiable information - Your information is collected when you register or fill in a form on a ARA-UK.com Ltd website, or you send an email to ARA-UK.com Ltd.. The information that is provided by you will only be used for the purpose for which it is provided, unless you are informed otherwise at the time of giving the information. You may inform ARA-UK.com Ltd. at any time if you wish ARA-UK.com Ltd. to cease using your personal information.   
Non identifiable information – ARA-UK.com Ltd. will from time to time collect information from you that does not reveal your personal identity, for example we may ask you to complete online polls. ARA-UK.com Ltd. uses this information for editorial purposes, and occasionally for other internal purposes. This information is only used in aggregate form and is not connected to any name, address or other personal identifying information. 

From time to time we may require personal information such as your official personal ID (such as passport/driving licence). This information will only be requested in certain circumstances, and only when required. We will not sell or give any personal information of our members to 3rd party companies and all information we receive is kept confidential. 

**How we use personal information**  
ARA-UK.com Ltd. processes personal information for the purpose of providing a personalised service, running competitions and providing you with information about products and services on offer. ARA-UK.com Ltd. may from time to time use your contact information to tell you about news or events provided by ARA-UK.com Ltd. or one of its strategic partners. You may opt-out of receiving such mailings at any time during your membership with ARA-UK.com Ltd.. ARA-UK.com Ltd. may also contact you with important information about your registration details even if you have opted-out of receiving promotional emails. User information such as your e-mail, password and AlertPay address will never be revealed to 3rd party companies. 

**International Transfers**  
ARA-UK.com Ltd. shall take steps to ensure that any transfer of data to a country or territory outside the European Economic Area, whose laws provide for a different standard of protection for your personal data than that provided under English law, shall be made subject to contractual arrangements which will require that your data be processed to at least a standard compliant with the Data Protection Act 1998 and the Electronic Communications Regulations 2003. 

**Links & Security**  
There are links on ARA-UK.com Ltd. web sites to third party web sites which ARA-UK.com Ltd. has no control over. ARA-UK.com Ltd. accepts no responsibility or liability for any third party practices on third party websites. Data transmission over the Internet is never totally secure and whilst ARA-UK.com Ltd. tries to protect your personal information, ARA-UK.com Ltd. cannot warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. 

**Cookies and other tracking devices**  
Cookies are information that are sent to and stored on your computer. They are used to identify you when you visit our sites. Cookies are used to remember usernames, passwords and your preferences. ARA-UK.com Ltd. websites may contain advertisements created and provided by third parties. These advertisements may also place Cookies on your computer that collect information about your use of the Internet. ARA-UK.com Ltd. does not control the collection or use of your information by such advertisers and our privacy policy does not apply to such information. 

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us by sending a support ticket.
